Start the exploitation section of the file we have collected in the collection.
So you need to kind of think on this in our clone and another one is a mega account.
Let me show you something.
Here you can see the our own downloads.
You can download the our own from this by clicking this.
Once you download the our home, just put it in your Apache directory.
So I mean here, so we know how to do that and transfer this to the Windows nation.
Okay.
So this is the thing you need to do before starting this.
I don't want to duplicate the task because you know people how to handle the how to handle
the third you deal, okay.
So you people know how to do that.
So you can you can use this technique and you can find you can download that.
Okay.
So once you have once you have downloaded the up one into the target machine, so the
next thing you need a mega account.
So you can go to Google and make a login, go to the sign up page and you can create your
own up.
Okay.
I already created.
I just created a folder.
The folder creation is simple.
You can create name the folder.
And you can create that go inside the folders, nothing was there, even this folder, nothing
was there.
Okay.
Let's just simple step, let's move to the calling environment and start in packet, let's
read to the mega, which I have uploaded, let's speak various, yeah, here is the, okay.
Let me add folder, let's take one more thing, nothing there, okay, again, we have a folder
let's go there, cool, let's queue the are now, so now we can find our code.exe, right.
So, let's execute the are for the XC, so now we need to configure the open with mega, let's
do that for configuration session, let's queue config, so now it was asking new remote,
I'll you in, they're going to sit in and enter the name for a remote, new remote, let
me you mega, and we have set of cloud, Amazon, black, black days, Citrix, a lot of things
right, a drop box, Google for age, a lot of things here, Google photo, $50, a lot of things
here, let's take the mega, we are going to upload it to mega, let's take that on $49,
so it was asking for a new, the name, let's need to give a new, the name, which account
you have, it was asking for a password, let me give me a password here.
We need to enter the, it was configuration, so we don't need any kind of advanced configuration,
so the configuration is good as of now, and keep this mega remote, it was asking, yeah,
let's keep this as a remote, and we have configured the data successfully now, so now what
we can do, let's put this configuration, and let's go to our clone, LS to mega, let's
let me list the remote, our clone, list, emotes, so now we have a mega configured, our clone,
LS for, list the directory inside the mega, is to, let's wait for some time, it needs
to list two directories, we have two directories, let's see, okay, it was not running, let
me go to, it was, and, so as well, so, sometime it will take some time, okay, it will to create, I'll do the picture of the column, I'll do it.
Sorry guys, after a few, we should troubleshoot, I can understand, the DNS server was, the DNS
server was not configured on the target machine properly, so this machine, I just top
off the video and configure the DNS server, that's all, I didn't perform any other things,
let's, to from the beginning, so this is enough, complicated stuff, we need to do it, but
organization machine, there is pre-configured DNS server, everything, they'll be configured,
but in our machine, if something, some settings get missed, like DNS, it will not work, okay,
so, in turn machine, I have some error in the DNS, okay, so that, I just correct her, let's see now how it will be
working, yeah, I can understand, this steps are like, huge, time-consuming, sorry about that, but
we need to do that anyway, R, R, R, R close, R close, a less of a remote, okay, R
clone, yeah, now we got it, so this is the output we need, you can see now we have two
names, so, here you can find the AJAway and Excel photos here, let's do the Excel, so we are
good with now, copy this, and then this time, sorry.
Now, let's see if it was uploading, I hope it will, it will upload the things, yeah, see now
we have the uploaded Excel dump.rat, sorry about this video, because I just has an error in the
DNS server, but I will do one thing, I will involve the other video to the previous case I have
handled, okay, sorry, the previous course I have taken, I have included that video, so if you guys
watch both of the video, you can properly understand what was happened, and how to configure
the maker and everything, so I know it's a bit complicated, but it's a very, very easy
thing, so the only error in my system that was like, the mega will be, will need proper
DNS thing, so you need to go to the control panel, I just did a one thing, and network
sharing sender, so ethernet properties, so nothing special, I just configured the DNS as
a.a. data date, and one.one.one.one.one, okay, so this is the things I just missed, because
if if we didn't set the DNS server to a.a. data date, or one.one.one, so the computer was
not able to reach the mega.a.t server, so there was some problems here, I just configured
this one thing, and now the mega was working properly for me, here you can find that,
so for your understanding, I will involve the other Rcon video to, for a better understand,
but this video is enough to get clear understanding about the Rcon, okay, I hope you have
a clear understanding about this one, I will involve another video, let's pop up from here,
and we'll continue our discussion in the next video, see you guys, bye bye.